[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The deficiency of vitamin C leads to this disease, which can be lethal.", "correct_answer": "Scurvy", "incorrect_answers": ["Influenza", "Meningitis", "Cancer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first word addressed to Mission Control by Neil Armstrong, when his craft landed on the Moon on July 20, 1969?", "correct_answer": "Houston", "incorrect_answers": ["One", "Buzz", "Roger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This bird is the fastest animal on the planet in its hunting method, the stoop.", "correct_answer": "Peregrine Falcon", "incorrect_answers": ["Bald Eagle", "Red-tailed Hawk", "Golden Eagle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 7-year-old pilot trainee died in her attempt to become the youngest person to fly a plane across the United States.", "correct_answer": "Jessica Dubroff", "incorrect_answers": ["Lisa Blair Hathaway", "Lisa Dubroff", "Jane Hathaway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the game of Mahjong, these red, white and green tiles are considered honor tiles, and are worth more as pongs and kongs than suit tile pongs and kongs.", "correct_answer": "Dragons", "incorrect_answers": ["Flowers", "Winds", "Birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the average weight of a Stegosaurus?", "correct_answer": "6,800 lbs. (3 tonnes)", "incorrect_answers": ["8,000 lbs. (3.6 tonnes)", "6,000 lbs. (2.7 tonnes)", "7,400 lbs. (3.3 tonnes)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from Pirates of the Caribbean said the following words: What do you say to three schillings, and we forget the name??", "correct_answer": "Jack Sparrow", "incorrect_answers": ["The dock-keeper", "Will Turner", "Captain Barbossa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor starred in the Hollywood production White Noise (2005).", "correct_answer": "Michael Keaton", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Hanks", "Nicolas Cage", "John Travolta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What statement is true about the sword duel between Drake and Blade in Blade Trinity?", "correct_answer": "Dominic Purcell (Drake) did all his stunts.", "incorrect_answers": ["The swords were fake.", "It was originally left out of the movie.", "Its all digital."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1994 animated movie The Lion King was inspired by this play by William Shakespeare.", "correct_answer": "Hamlet", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Romeo and Juliet", "Othello"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following abbreviations pertains to a diagnosis?", "correct_answer": "ICD-9 Code", "incorrect_answers": ["EM Code", "CPT Code", "G-code"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which daikaij\u016b (giant monster) most resembles a turtle?", "correct_answer": "Gamera", "incorrect_answers": ["Gigan", "Ghidora", "Godzilla"]}]